

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Details

16 west 325 hole Sanya, 36521 China 18242316839

mark@hypersoftwares.com

DATE OF EIRT

1987-10-01

Links

Twitter

Guru

Skype

Skills

Solidity

Node.js

Blockchain

C#, C++

ASP

Hybrid Mobile App

PHP

React

WordPress

AWS

JavaScript

ChatGPT

Languages

English

Chinese

Profile

Hello

I have been working as a Blockchain developer since 2016 and I have many experiences in skills.

Smart Contract, Dapp, Defi, PoW(PoS) networks, etc).

I worked on several NFT projects and smart contract development, I have enough skills, and knowledge for them.

Example:: @RoaringLeaders, @digitzNFT, @MetaOneStudios and @HeadDaoNFT.

Also, AI/ML projects and online store development are my major skills.

https://aicodx.com/, https://deteconology.com/, and several ChatBot, LLM projects

Thanks

Employment History

Software Developer, assured Techmatics, Doral

MARCH 2016 - MAY 2018

Website development, Rest API, Web application development

I worked in the role of company website build and manage and track API for truck movement.

Web Developer & Manager, motorcyclepartz, Doral

MARCH 2014 - AUGUST 2018

Web Developer

Blockchain Developer & Tech leader, RChain Tech, Beijing

JANUARY 2016 - MARCH 2021

https://www.linkedin.com/company/rchain-tech

There I worked several company-related jobs and in there include this work role.

High-performance crypto exchange development (IEO) and ICO, STO smart contract & manage panel development

EVM and another blockchain network hard fork and PoS, PoC network development

Smart Contract Developer, Roaring Leaders, New York City

NOVEMBER 2020 - JULY 2021

In EVM config NFT project's smart contract development & Audit.

Minting Dapp page build and utility token create and community tech skills

https://linktr.ee/roaringleaders

Web Manager, hypersoftwares.com, London

NOVEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

Several web & mobile application development/manager

Education

Tsinghua University, Beijing

APRIL 2008 - OCTOBER 2012

Computer Software Engineer

Yeshiva & Misivta Tiferes Elimelech

References

Jimmy from Callffry

Courses

Certified Enterprise Blockchain Professional

Blockchain Talents Labs Course

Extra-curricular activities

Online Store Development, Shopify

Online Store Development